# **Howard Jiang**

Phone: (646)-886-9161 Email: Howard.Jiang76@myhunter.cuny.edu

## Summary

Experienced sales associate with four years in retail apparel, cell phone accessory and jewelry sales. Friendly, outgoing, and charismatic personality well suited for a fast paced, customer service oriented establishments and ensures that customers leave the premises satisfied. Meticulous worker; attentive to quality and detail.

### Education

#### **Hunter College CUNY**

September 2016 - Present

- Majoring in Computer science, GPA: 3.4/4.0
- Expected graduation: May 30, 2020

#### Brooklyn Technical High School

Brooklyn, NY, September 2012 - June 2016

- Concentration in Software Engineering and received a high school diploma.
- Member of Brooklyn Technical High School's H.O.P.E. and Outreach clubs; volunteered for community service events hosted by the clubs.

# **Experiences**

#### Classy Jewelry Wholesale Inc.

Manhattan, NY, September 2015 – Present

- Manage and maintain stock of over 1,000 items.
- Prepare products for consumption.
- Greet customers and ask if they need any assistance.
- Assist customers with product knowledge and pricing.
- Help customers make selections by offering suggestions and opinions when needed.
- Build and process customer invoices that total over \$300 daily.

#### Café Bene

#### Koreatown Manhattan, NY, August 2016 – October 2016

- Process customer orders through the PoS system.
- Quickly prepare orders consisting of/including bubble tea, sandwiches, honey bread, patbingsu, and snowflakes.
- Answer customers questions and provide information on procedures or policies.
- Maintain a clean and orderly workspace by: mopping floors, emptying trash, cleaning the premises, and placing items in their appropriate places.
- Regularly restock any items that are missing for the next day.

## **Community Service**

# Regal Heights Rehabilitation and Health Care Center

Queens, NY, June 2013 - June 2014

- Brought elders from to their designations.
- Entertained the elderly through one to one visits, balloon toss, trivia, and other activities.
- Hosted a bingo event with twenty elders present, gave out prizes to the winners in the form of money, and settled quarrels that occurred.
- Logged each interaction with elders and made sure paperwork was properly sorted and up to date.

#### Skills

- Easily adapts to new situations and environments.
- Highly responsible and reliable.
- Works well under pressure.
- Extensive hospitality background.
- Conversational in Mandarin and Wenzhounese.
- Programing/languages: C++, Python, Html

#### References

References available upon request.